fetcher.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy - Fetcher

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.fetcher.com and Fetcher LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Fetcher LLC include www.fetcher.com and Fetcher. The Fetcher website is a software service site. By using the Fetcher website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Fetcher may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Fetcher’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non–personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Fetcher. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Fetcher website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Fetcher’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Fetcher encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Fetcher so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Fetcher is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Fetcher website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Fetcher collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Fetcher may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Fetcher and its affiliates. Fetcher may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Fetcher does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Fetcher may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Fetcher, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Fetcher may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Fetcher, in order to determine what Fetcher services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Fetcher to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Fetcher will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Fetcher or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Fetcher; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Fetcher, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Fetcher secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Fetcher does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt–out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt–out of receiving any or all communications from Fetcher by contacting us here: support@fetcher.com

**Changes to this Statement**

Fetcher will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Fetcher encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Fetcher is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Fetcher welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Fetcher has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Fetcher at:  
Fetcher LLC  
818 SW 3rd Ave #221-5422  
Portland, Oregon 97204  
Email Address: support@fetcher.com  
Effective as of October 01, 2016
